SARAH COX-BARKLEY

Island Lake, Illinois
Phone: 815-355-0329 | Email: sarahl.cox.22@gmail.com
LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/sarahlcox22 | GitHub: github.com/sarahlcox
Portfolio: sarahlcox.github.io/updated-portfolio-sarahbarkley/

SUMMARY

Full Stack Web Developer with a background in photography, business management, real estate, and English studies. Has an urgency to learn and develop new skills, and has a wide array of experience, and interests. Passionate about helping other companies fine-tune their online presence. Maintains a fresh, creative perspective when it comes to web development and branding, while remaining professional, and teachable.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: JavaScript, ES6+, CSS, HTML, SQL **Applications:** GitHub, Heroku, MySQL, WordPress

Tools: Express, React, Node, Handlebars, Query, Bootstrap, **Programs:** Visual Studio Code, Adobe Suite, Hootsuite,

PROJECTS

Vote 2020 | github.com/B-Dionysus/project1-Election | https://b-dionysus.github.io/project1-Election/index.html

- Short summary of project (1-2 lines)
- Developing the
- Tools / languages used

EXPERIENCE

Small Business Owner

Feather Print Photography & Media | 2010 - Present Lifestyle family, wedding, and small business branding photographer, that also specializes in WordPress services. Manage all social media, blogs, websites, finances, and client relations.

- Oversee day-to-day operations and finances
- Manage social media and online presence
- Content marketing editor
- Video storyline and editing
- Maintain websites and keep websites search engine optimized
- Provide outstanding customer service
- Photograph, edit, and sell sessions, products, and services to prospective clients

Licensed Real Estate Assistant and Broker

The Paula Schatz Team Inc. | 2016 - 2019 Responsible for team promotion on social media platforms, website design and maintenance, and provide real estate services to clients

- Content marketing editor
- Provide clients with upstanding and professional real estate service
- Manage client follow-up and lead generation
- Oversee day-to-day operations
- Tech support
- Design and production of manuals, brochures, and direct mailings

Administrative Assistant

The Pattie Taylor Team | 2014 - 2016 Maintain an organized real estate office, design print material, and collect data from past clients on their experience

- Organize and manage real estate office
- Content marketing and copywriter
- Manage and organize client follow-up
- Design print material
- Photograph and video property listings

Sales Representative/Photographer/Administrative Assistant

Bella Baby Photography | 2009 - 2015 Provide an amazing first photography experience for new parents while selling products and future services. Offer administrative support for Bella Baby Midwest Region.

- Responsible for managing photographs for local hospitals
- Interact with patients and nursing staff to provide quality customer service
- Creatively photograph newborns to generate high sales volume
- Fulfill and ship online orders for Bella Baby Midwest Region
- Certified as a weekend manager to provide support to over 20+ employees

Director of Operations

The Sharron Kelley Team | 2012 - 2014 Responsible for marketing, website maintenance, blogging, and customer relationship management

- Social media, blog, and website
- Market all properties and company
- Manage client follow-up and lead generation
- Oversee day-to-day operations
- Design and production of manuals and brochures

EDUCATION

Bootcamp Certificate - 2020: Northwestern University, Evanston, Illinois A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handelbars.js & ReactJS.

Bachelor of Arts, English 2008-2012: Northern Illinois University, DeKalb, Illinois